Guide to the Archives Union File Part 2, Section 3: Boxes 130-143 1872-1976
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 3: Boxes 130-143
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 3: Boxes 130-143, 1872-1976
6374 PUBS
Brown University Library
77.8 linear ft.
Publications.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The Archives Union File Part 2 is a collection of printed ephemeral documents, issued primarily by trade unions and labor organizations.
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into three sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-65
Section 2: Boxes 66-129
Section 3: Boxes 130-143
SUBJECTS
Names:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
Subjects:
American Federation of Railroad Workers; Associated Industries f Massachusetts; Association of Catholic Trade Unionists (ACTU); Atlantic Deeper Waterways Association; Bartenders International League of America; Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (BLE); Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen (BLF&E); Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen (BRT); Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Agents (BRAC); Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters; Building Service Employees' International Union; Chase Bank Club of New York; Chicago Federation of Labor; Council of Europe; Hotel and Restaurant Employes International Alliance; International Association of Car Workers; International Association of Machinists (AIM); International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW); International Brotherhood of Paper Makers; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU); International Seamen's Union of America; International Union of Steam Engineers; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW); Journeymen Tailors' Union of America; Labor Record; Labour Party; Manufacturers' Record Publishing Company; National Association of Manufacturers; National Manufacturers Company; National Metal Trades Association; New York State Teachers Association (NYSTA); Order of Railroad Telegraphers (ORC); S. P. Dinsmore and Co.; Sailors' Union of the Pacific; Service Employees International Union (SEIU); Standard Oil Company; Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA); The National Underwriter Company; Transport Union of America (TUA); Transport Workers Union of America; U.S. President's Commission on the Status of Women; United Brotherhood of Leather Workers on Horse Goods; United Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes; United Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes and Railway Shop Laborers; United Garment Workers of America; United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Works International Union; United Leather Workers International Union; United Nations; United Office and Professional Workers of America; United Papermakers and Paperworkers; United Steelworkers of America (USWA)
Form and Genre Terms:
Publications
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Related Collections:
5582: Archives Foreign File (AFF)
5583: Archives Organization File (AOF)
5583 AV: Archives Organization File (AOF) Audio-Visual Materials
5880: Archives Organization File V, Additional Company Documents
5956: Archives Organization File Additional Records
6046: Archives Union File (AUF)
6046 mf: Archives Union File on Microfilm
6374 PUBS: Archives Union File Part 2
6374 PUBS: Archives Union File Part 2, Section 1: Boxes 1-65
6374 PUBS: Archives Union File Part 2, Section 2: Boxes 66-129
CONTAINER LIST
- The Tailor, 1918-1919 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Author: Journeymen Tailors' Union of America
    Notes: v.29:no.1 (1918: July 30)
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.2 (1918: Aug. 6)
  - Item 3: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.4 (1918: Aug. 20)
  - Item 4: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.5 (1918: Aug. 27)
  - Item 5: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.6 (1918: Sept. 3)
  - Item 6: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.7 (1918: Sept. 10)
  - Item 7: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.8 (1918: Sept. 17)
  - Item 8: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.9 (1918: Sept. 24)
  - Item 9: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.10 (1918: Oct. 1)
  - Item 10: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.11 (1918: Oct. 8)
  - Item 11: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.12 (1918: Oct. 15)
  - Item 12: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.13 (1918: Oct. 22)
  - Item 13: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.14 (1918: Oct. 29)
  - Item 14: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.15 (1918: Nov. 5)
  - Item 15: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.16 (1918: Nov. 12)
  - Item 16: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.17 (1918: Nov. 19)
  - Item 17: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.18 (1918: Nov. 26)
  - Item 18: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.19 (1918: Dec. 3)
  - Item 19: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.20 (1918: Dec. 10)
  - Item 20: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.21 (1918: Dec. 17)
  - Item 21: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.22 (1918: Dec. 24)
  - Item 22: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.23 (1918: Dec. 31)
  - Item 23: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.24 (1919: Jan. 7)
  - Item 24: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.25 (1919: Jan. 14)
  - Item 25: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.26 (1919: Jan. 21)
  - Item 26: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.27 (1919: Jan. 24)
  - Item 27: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.28 (1919: Feb. 4)
  - Item 28: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.29 (1919: Feb. 11)
  - Item 29: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.30 (1919: Feb. 18)
  - Item 30: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.31 (1919: Feb. 25)
  - Item 31: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.32 (1919: Mar. 4)
  - Item 32: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.33 (1919: Mar. 11)
  - Item 33: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.35 (1919: Mar. 25)
  - Item 34: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.36 (1919: Apr. 1)
  - Item 35: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.37 (1919: Apr. 8)
  - Item 36: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.38 (1919: Apr. 15)
  - Item 37: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.39 (1919: Apr. 22)
  - Item 38: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.40 (1919: Apr. 29)
  - Item 39: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.41 (1919: May 6)
  - Item 40: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.42 (1919: May 13)
  - Item 41: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.43 (1919: May 20)
  - Item 42: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.44 (1919: May 27)
  - Item 43: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.45 (1919: June 3)
  - Item 44: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.46 (1919: June 10)
  - Item 45: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.47 (1919: June 17)
  - Item 46: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.48 (1919: June 24)
  - Item 47: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.49 (1919: July 1)
  - Item 48: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.50 (1919: July 8)
  - Item 49: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.51 (1919: July 15)
  - Item 50: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.51 (1919: July 15). Copy 2.
  - Item 51: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.52 (1919: July 22)
- The Tailor, 1919-1920 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.1 (1919: July 29)
  - Item 2: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.2 (1919: Aug. 5)
  - Item 3: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.3 (1919: Aug. 12)
  - Item 4: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.4 (1919: Aug. 19)
  - Item 5: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.6 (1919: Sept. 2)
  - Item 6: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.7 (1919: Sept. 9)
  - Item 7: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.8 (1919: Sept. 16)
  - Item 8: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.9 (1919: Sept. 23)
  - Item 9: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.10 (1919: Sept. 30)
  - Item 10: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.11 (1919: Oct. 7)
  - Item 11: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.12 (1919: Oct. 14)
  - Item 12: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.13 (1919: Oct. 21)
  - Item 13: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.14 (1919: Oct. 28)
  - Item 14: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.15 (1919: Nov. 4)
  - Item 15: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.16 (1919: Nov. 11)
  - Item 16: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.17 (1919: Nov. 18)
  - Item 17: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.19 (1919: Dec. 2)
  - Item 18: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.21 (1919: Dec. 16)
  - Item 19: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.22 (1919: Dec. 23)
  - Item 20: The Tailor, 1919; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.23 (1919: Dec. 30)
  - Item 21: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.24 (1920: Jan. 6)
  - Item 22: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.26 (1920: Jan. 20)
  - Item 23: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.27 (1920: Jan. 27)
  - Item 24: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.28 (1920: Feb. 3)
  - Item 25: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.29 (1920: Feb. 10)
  - Item 26: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.30 (1920: Feb. 17)
  - Item 27: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.31 (1920: Feb. 24)
  - Item 28: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.32 (1920: Mar. 2)
  - Item 29: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.33 (1920: Mar. 9)
  - Item 30: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.35 (1920: Mar. 23)
  - Item 31: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.36 (1920: Mar. 30)
  - Item 32: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.37 (1920: Apr. 6)
  - Item 33: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.38 (1920: Apr. 13)
  - Item 34: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.39 (1920: Apr. 20)
  - Item 35: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.40 (1920: Apr. 27)
  - Item 36: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.41 (1920: May 4)
  - Item 37: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.42 (1920: May 18)
  - Item 38: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.43 (1920: June 1)
  - Item 39: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.44 (1920: June 15)
  - Item 40: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.45 (1920: June 29)
  - Item 41: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.46 (1920: July 13)
  - Item 42: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.47 (1920: July 27)
  - Item 43: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.48 (1920: Aug. 10)
  - Item 44: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.49 (1920: Aug. 24)
  - Item 45: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.50 (1920: sept. 7)
  - Item 46: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.51 (1920: Sept. 21)
  - Item 47: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.52 (1920: Oct. 5)
- The Tailor, 1920-1923 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.1 (1920: Oct. 19)
  - Item 2: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.2 (1920: Nov. 2)
  - Item 3: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.3 (1920: Nov. 16)
  - Item 4: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.4 (1920: Nov. 30)
  - Item 5: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.5 (1920: Dec. 14)
  - Item 6: The Tailor, 1920; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.6 (1920: Dec. 28)
  - Item 7: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.7 (1921: Jan. 11)
  - Item 8: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.8 (1921: Jan. 25)
  - Item 9: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.9 (1921: Feb. 8)
  - Item 10: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.10 (1921: Feb. 22)
  - Item 11: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.11 (1921: Mar. 8)
  - Item 12: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.13 (1921: Apr. 5)
  - Item 13: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.14 (1921: Apr. 19)
  - Item 14: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.15 (1921: May 3)
  - Item 15: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.16 (1921: May 17)
  - Item 16: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.19 (1921: June 28)
  - Item 17: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.20 (1921: July 12)
  - Item 18: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.21 (1921: July 26)
  - Item 19: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.22 (1921: Aug. 9)
  - Item 20: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.23 (1921: Aug. 23)
  - Item 21: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.24 (1921: Sept. 6)
  - Item 22: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.25 (1921: Sept. 20)
  - Item 23: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.26 (1921: Oct. 4)
  - Item 24: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.1 (1921: Oct. 18)
  - Item 25: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.2 (1921: Nov. 1)
  - Item 26: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.3 (1921: Nov. 15)
  - Item 27: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.4 (1921: Nov. 29)
  - Item 28: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.5 (1921: Dec. 13)
  - Item 29: The Tailor, 1921; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.6 (1921: Dec. 27)
  - Item 30: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.7 (1922: Jan. 10)
  - Item 31: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.8 (1922: Jan. 24)
  - Item 32: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.9 (1922: Feb. 7)
  - Item 33: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.10 (1922: Feb. 21)
  - Item 34: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.11 (1922: Mar. 7)
  - Item 35: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.12 (1922: Mar. 21)
  - Item 36: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.13 (1922: Apr. 4)
  - Item 37: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.14 (1922: Apr. 18)
  - Item 38: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.15 (1922: May 2)
  - Item 39: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.16 (1922: May 16)
  - Item 40: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.17 (1922: May 30)
  - Item 41: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.18 (1922: June 13)
  - Item 42: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.19 (1922: June 27)
  - Item 43: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.20 (1922: July 11)
  - Item 44: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.21 (1922: July 25)
  - Item 45: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.22 (1922: Aug. 8)
  - Item 46: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.23 (1922: Aug. 22)
  - Item 47: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.24 (1922: Sept. 5)
  - Item 48: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.25 (1922: Sept. 19)
  - Item 49: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.26 (1922: Oct. 3)
  - Item 50: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.1 (1922: Oct. 17)
  - Item 51: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.2 (1922: Oct. 31)
  - Item 52: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.3 (1922: Nov. 14)
  - Item 53: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.4 (1922: Nov. 28)
  - Item 54: The Tailor, 1922; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.5 (1922: Dec. 12)
  - Item 55: The Tailor, 1923; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.7 (1923: Jan. 9)
  - Item 56: The Tailor, 1923; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.8 (1923: Jan. 23)
  - Item 57: The Tailor, 1923; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.9 (1923: Feb. 6)
  - Item 58: The Tailor, 1923; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.10 (1923: Feb. 20)
  - Item 59: The Tailor, 1923; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.11 (1923: Mar. 6)
  - Item 60: The Tailor, 1923; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.12 (1923: Mar. 20)
  - Item 61: The Tailor, 1923; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.13 (1923: Apr. 3)
  - Item 62: The Tailor, 1923; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.14 (1923: Apr. 17)
  - Item 63: The Tailor, 1923; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.15 (1923: May 1)
  - Item 64: The Tailor, 1923; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.16 (1923: May 15)
  - Item 65: The Tailor, 1923; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.17 (1923: May 29)
  - Item 66: The Tailor, 1923; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.18 (1923: June 12)
  - Item 67: The Tailor, 1923; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.19 (1923: June 26)
  - Item 68: The Tailor, 1923; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.20 (1923: July 10)
  - Item 69: The Tailor, 1923; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.21 (1923: July 24)
  - Item 70: The Tailor, 1923; Publication (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.22 (1923: Aug. 7)
- This Week, 1962-1963 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Author: Labour Party
    Notes: v.4:no.1 (1962: Jan. 4)
  - Item 2: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.2 (1962: Jan. 11)
  - Item 3: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.3 (1962: Jan. 25)
  - Item 4: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.4 (1962: Feb. 1)
  - Item 5: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.5 (1962: Feb. 8)
  - Item 6: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.6 (1962: Feb. 15)
  - Item 7: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.7 (1962: Feb. 22)
  - Item 8: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.8 (1962: Feb. 29)
  - Item 9: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.9 (1962: Mar. 8)
  - Item 10: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.10 (1962: Mar. 15)
  - Item 11: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.11 (1962: Mar. 22)
  - Item 12: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.12 (1962: Mar. 29)
  - Item 13: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.13 (1962: Apr. 5)
  - Item 14: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.14 (1962: Apr. 12)
  - Item 15: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.15 (1962: Apr. 19)
  - Item 16: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.16 (1962: May 10)
  - Item 17: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.17 (1962: May 17)
  - Item 18: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.18 (1962: May 24)
  - Item 19: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.19 (1962: May 31)
  - Item 20: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.20 (1962: June 7)
  - Item 21: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.21 (1962: June 28)
  - Item 22: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.22 (1962: July 5)
  - Item 23: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.23 (1962: July 12)
  - Item 24: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.24 (1962: July 19)
  - Item 25: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.25 (1962: July 26)
  - Item 26: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.26 (1962: Aug. 2)
  - Item 27: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.27 (1962: Sept. 6)
  - Item 28: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.28 (1962: Sept. 13)
  - Item 29: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.29 (1962: Sept. 20)
  - Item 30: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.30 (1962: Sept. 27)
  - Item 31: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.31 (1962: Oct. 4)